Guide to the Susan G. Bell papers SC1287
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2016-109
  - Worthern Lady Martin Holmes (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (in Shipton v Whyewood) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - unlabeled (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - 1964 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - 1966 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - 1958 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - 1960 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - 1961 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - 1962 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - 1959 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - 1963 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Address books (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Audrey German Xmas ornaments (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence personal A-F (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Negatives (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Negatives (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Ms. Sue Bell (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - European info correspondence, 1973 Summer (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sue's mother's letters and photographs (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Diascop (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Books (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Cards (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cards (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Cards (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 2007 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 2009 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 2010 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 2011 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 2012 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 2013 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 2014 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Overseas Bulletin, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - OLOMOUC (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 1950 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - 1954 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - 1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - 1996 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - 2001 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - 2003 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Cards (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Cards (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Cards (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Cards (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Letters from LBH, Florence Helevy, Ruth Dalton, 1950 Jul, 1960 Nov (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Autograph letter, 1835 Aug 5 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Autograph letters, 1778-1827 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Goodspeed's book shop, 1967 Oct (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Sept. 1967 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Rare books section pre-conference, 1967 Jun 22-24 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Mrs. R. Bell, 1974 Nov 27 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - 1907 Apr 19 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - 1967 Oct 30 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - A curious early will, 1652 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - First chapters (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Business cards SGB (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Second careers for women (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - 1959 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - 1950 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - 1950 Apr 17 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Mrs. Roberts (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Public health department note, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Thank you letters, 1956 May 7 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Dates (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - 1950 Nov (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Ballroom - Stone Cross Hall, circa 1953 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - 1900 Feb 8 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - 2009 Dec (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - 2009 Jun 30 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - 2010 Jan 1 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - 2009 Dec 21 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - 2008 Apr 6 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Holiday cards (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - 205 Jun 2 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - 1948 May 25 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - 1948 Nov (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Old letters cards - Ct. Clair (Box 21, Folder 63)